Weite Dai

0414657767 | weitedai.dev@gmail.com | Hobart https://www.linkedin.com/in/weitedai/ | https://github.com/weited

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A dedicated and passionate full stack developer with 2 years coding experience in web development from LAMP to MERN stack. Great communication skills and problem solving skills with Agile/Scrum experience Active learner always like to learn knowledge.

SKILLS

Front End:

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript ES6, React.js, Redux, Material UI, Bootstrap, Antd, Responsive Design, NPM/YARN. babel. ESlint

Back End:

Node.js, Express.js, JWT token, PHP, mongoose, winston

DevOps:

AWS S3 CDN Lambda ECS, PM2, Docker, Nginx, Heroku, AliCloud ECS OSS, LAMP, CI/CD,

API:

RESTful, Swagger, Axios, Postman

Other tools/platforms/methodologies:

Agile, Scrum, Sprint, Jira, Git, Github, Bitbucket, Figma, JestTest

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Brain Cells

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

Full-stack Developer Remote

https://quicklearner.io/

Discription:

A greenfield project using React.js and Node.js named quicklearner which is an online quiz platform for people to create and share their guizzes for education or entertainment use.

Team:

Worked in an Agile team with 9 developers, 1 BA and 4 DevOps through Jira Agile/Scrum.

Responsibility & Achievement

- Designed data structure based on the business requirements and implemented data model.
- Implemented the web app front end with HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript(ES6), React.js, Redux, React
 Router, Material UI
- Implemented the web app back end RESTfull API with Node.js, Express.js, JWT token, Morgan, Bcrypt, Mongoose.
- Developed RESTful API documentation with Swagger UI to increase effectiveness between front and back end.

- Developed Axios encapsulation for API requests unified management and handle responses centralizedly
- Implemented log tool for back end using Winston to save various kinds of error level and different resulet based on environment.
- Experienced continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) through AWS and implemented Docker stack for development and production.
- · Implemeted AWS lambda serverless

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Portfolio Website Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

Web developer

- Designed and developed a portfolio website for custom to display customer's resume, skills and work experiences.
- Implemeted HTML5, CSS3, Javascript(ES6), SASS, Bootstrap, SEO, Resposive design.
- · Optimised UI/UX for user.
- Implemeted git and github action for CI/CD.
- · Deployed to AWS S3.
- Deployed to server with Nginx and implemeted reverse proxy to host the web.

Stroke Rehabilitation App

Mar 2022 - Jun 2022

Hobart

Mobile developer

• Designed and developed mobile application on three platforms including Android, iOS and Cross Platform.

- developed Android app with Kotlin/Java, iOS with Swift and Cross platform app with Flutter.
- · Implemented nosql database Firebase.

Online shopping website

Mar 2022 - May 2022

Full-stack developer

An online shopping website using React.js, Node.js and MySQL

- Implemented the web front end with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript(ES6), React.js, ANTD
- Implemented two back end apps with Node.js, Express.js, MySQL and REST full API
- · Deployed back end into two VMs for load balance
- Deployed back end app with Docker and implemented Nginx for reverse proxy.
- · Deployed back end app with pm2 and implemented Apache for reverse proxy.

EDUCATION

JR Academy Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

Full-stack Development Remote
University of Tasmania Mar 2021 - Nov 2022

Master of Information Technology and Systems

Hobart

- Intelligent and Secure Web Development (PHP/Node.js, MVC)
- Software Application Design and Implementation (C#, SDLC, Agile, MySQL)
- Web Development (PHP, jQuery, AJAX)
- Mobile development (Kotlin/Java, Swift, Flutter, firebase)